<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Veritas</string>
    <string name="reason_generic_what">%1$s is one signal Veritas records during a scan. The detail depends on the media type and the measurements attached to this result.</string>
    <string name="reason_generic_why">%1$s matters only in context. Veritas weighs it with the other detector and provenance signals before choosing a verdict.</string>
    <string name="reason_generic_risk">This signal is not proof by itself. Capture conditions, editing, platform recompression, or unusual source material can create similar measurements in authentic media.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_deepfake_model_high_label">SPATIAL</string>
    <string name="reason_img_deepfake_model_high_title">Generative image pattern</string>
    <string name="reason_img_deepfake_model_high_what">The image model found spatial and frequency patterns that are more common in generated imagery than in camera captures.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_deepfake_model_high_why">This is the strongest image signal because it comes from the detector trained on real and synthetic image examples. It is still interpreted with metadata and quality checks.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_deepfake_model_high_risk">Highly edited images, screenshots, low-quality reposts, and aggressive compression can make authentic images resemble generated samples.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_missing_label">EXIF</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_missing_title">Missing camera metadata</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_missing_what">No camera make, model, or capture metadata was found in the image file.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_missing_why">Real camera files often carry metadata, while generated images and platform exports often do not. Veritas treats this as supporting evidence only.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_missing_risk">Many authentic screenshots, social uploads, and privacy-preserving apps remove EXIF metadata.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_suspicious_label">METADATA</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_suspicious_title">Suspicious image encoding</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_suspicious_what">JPEG quantization or image metadata does not match common camera or editor export patterns.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_suspicious_why">Encoding fingerprints can reveal when an image was synthesized, re-saved, or assembled through an unusual toolchain.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_exif_suspicious_risk">Editing apps, memes, screenshots, and platform recompression can also produce unusual encoding fingerprints.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_ela_anomaly_label">ELA</string>
    <string name="reason_img_ela_anomaly_title">Error-level anomaly</string>
    <string name="reason_img_ela_anomaly_what">Error-level analysis found regions whose compression behavior differs from the surrounding image.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_ela_anomaly_why">Local compression differences can point to editing, compositing, or generated regions that were introduced after the original image was encoded.</string>
    <string name="reason_img_ela_anomaly_risk">Multiple saves, filters, stickers, and normal edits can create similar ELA differences in authentic images.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_synthetic_voice_high_label">VOICE</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_synthetic_voice_high_title">Synthetic voice pattern</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_synthetic_voice_high_what">The audio model found speech features that resemble neural voice generation or voice conversion.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_synthetic_voice_high_why">Voice-clone detectors are strongest when speech is clear and long enough to expose spectral and timing artifacts.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_synthetic_voice_high_risk">Noisy recordings, speakerphone audio, codec damage, and accented or unusual speech can reduce reliability.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_codec_mismatch_label">CODEC</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_codec_mismatch_title">Audio codec mismatch</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_codec_mismatch_what">The audio compression profile is less plausible for the file type and recording path.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_codec_mismatch_why">Synthetic clips are often exported, transcoded, or inserted into containers in ways that do not match natural phone recordings.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_codec_mismatch_risk">Messaging apps, editors, and screen recordings can transcode authentic audio into unusual profiles.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_too_short_label">SHORT</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_too_short_title">Audio too short</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_too_short_what">The clip does not contain enough speech for a reliable detector read.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_too_short_why">Short clips may not expose the spectral, timing, and prosody patterns needed to separate human and synthetic speech.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_too_short_risk">This is a confidence warning, not a synthetic signal. A short authentic clip can trigger it.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_natural_prosody_label">VOICE OK</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_natural_prosody_title">Natural speech signal</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_natural_prosody_what">The audio model did not find strong synthetic speech artifacts in this clip.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_natural_prosody_why">A clean speech signal lowers synthetic confidence when it agrees with codec and quality checks.</string>
    <string name="reason_aud_natural_prosody_risk">High-quality voice clones or heavily transformed audio can still evade this detector.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_spatial_synthetic_frames_label">FRAMES</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_spatial_synthetic_frames_title">Synthetic-looking frames</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_spatial_synthetic_frames_what">One or more sampled frames contain image-level patterns associated with generated visuals.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_spatial_synthetic_frames_why">Frame evidence helps localize where the detector saw suspicious content, especially when only part of a clip is synthetic.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_spatial_synthetic_frames_risk">Static-image evidence does not prove a temporal deepfake. Recompression, overlays, and stylized footage can trigger similar frame-level signals.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_temporal_drift_high_label">DRIFT</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_temporal_drift_high_title">Temporal drift</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_temporal_drift_high_what">The video model saw frame-to-frame embedding changes that were less consistent than expected for natural motion.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_temporal_drift_high_why">Temporal consistency can expose generation artifacts that are not visible in a single still frame.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_temporal_drift_high_risk">Fast cuts, screen recordings, stabilization, and low frame rates can also create abrupt temporal changes.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_face_inconsistent_label">FACE</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_face_inconsistent_title">Face consistency issue</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_face_inconsistent_what">Face-region analysis found a consistency score outside the expected range for the sampled frames.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_face_inconsistent_why">Face regions are high-value forensic areas because many manipulations concentrate around eyes, mouth, skin, and facial boundaries.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_face_inconsistent_risk">Small faces, motion blur, masks, makeup, occlusion, or unusual lighting can make face-region analysis less reliable.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_decode_failed_label">DECODE</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_decode_failed_title">Video decode failed</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_decode_failed_what">The video could not be decoded far enough for detector inference.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_decode_failed_why">Decoder failures explain why Veritas cannot make a confident visual or temporal claim about the clip.</string>
    <string name="reason_vid_decode_failed_risk">This is not evidence of manipulation. Corrupt downloads, unsupported encoders, or damaged files can cause the same result.</string>
    <string name="reason_codec_consistent_label">CODEC OK</string>
    <string name="reason_codec_consistent_title">Capture chain looks consistent</string>
    <string name="reason_codec_consistent_what">The media did not show strong codec or model signs of synthetic generation in this scan.</string>
    <string name="reason_codec_consistent_why">A clean negative signal helps avoid over-calling synthetic content when the detector evidence is weak.</string>
    <string name="reason_codec_consistent_risk">Absence of detected artifacts is not proof of authenticity, especially for high-quality generated media or heavily transformed reposts.</string>
    <string name="reason_quality_label">QUALITY</string>
    <string name="reason_quality_title">Quality-limited evidence</string>
    <string name="reason_quality_what">The scan was affected by low resolution, short duration, heavy compression, missing frames, or a runtime fallback.</string>
    <string name="reason_quality_why">Quality limits are surfaced because they explain why Veritas may return an uncertain verdict instead of forcing a binary answer.</string>
    <string name="reason_quality_risk">Quality warnings often come from ordinary platform recompression or old files. They reduce confidence rather than proving manipulation.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_verified_label">C2PA OK</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_verified_title">Signed Content Credentials</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_verified_what">The file contains a valid signed provenance manifest from a known issuer.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_verified_why">A valid signature can strongly support authenticity because it ties the file to a capture or editing chain.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_verified_risk">A valid manifest describes provenance, not absolute truth. It may not cover later screen recordings or copies.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_invalid_signature_label">C2PA BAD</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_invalid_signature_title">Invalid provenance signature</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_invalid_signature_what">The file claims Content Credentials, but the signature does not validate.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_invalid_signature_why">A forged or altered manifest is stronger tampering evidence than a file with no manifest at all.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_invalid_signature_risk">File corruption or broken export tools can also damage a manifest, so Veritas weighs this with other evidence.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_revoked_label">C2PA REV</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_revoked_title">Revoked signing authority</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_revoked_what">The signing authority for this file has been revoked since signing.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_revoked_why">Revocation means Veritas can no longer treat the signature as a clean authenticity signal.</string>
    <string name="reason_c2pa_revoked_risk">Revocation can happen for administrative reasons unrelated to this file.</string>
    <string name="reason_synthid_detected_label">SYNTHID</string>
    <string name="reason_synthid_detected_title">AI watermark detected</string>
    <string name="reason_synthid_detected_what">A known generator watermark signature was detected in the media.</string>
    <string name="reason_synthid_detected_why">Watermarks are direct provenance evidence when they survive export and recompression.</string>
    <string name="reason_synthid_detected_risk">Watermark availability depends on generator support and may be affected by cropping, recompression, or edits.</string>
    <string name="reason_diffusion_spectral_sig_label">FREQ</string>
    <string name="reason_diffusion_spectral_sig_title">Diffusion spectral signature</string>
    <string name="reason_diffusion_spectral_sig_what">Frequency-domain structure resembles artifacts left by diffusion-style image generation.</string>
    <string name="reason_diffusion_spectral_sig_why">Generated images can leave regular patterns that real camera optics and sensors usually do not create.</string>
    <string name="reason_diffusion_spectral_sig_risk">Scaling, sharpening, screenshots, and platform recompression can create misleading frequency patterns.</string>
    <string name="reason_ela_inconsistent_label">ELA</string>
    <string name="reason_ela_inconsistent_title">Inconsistent compression region</string>
    <string name="reason_ela_inconsistent_what">A localized region compresses differently from the surrounding media.</string>
    <string name="reason_ela_inconsistent_why">This can indicate a generated or edited region inserted into an otherwise different image.</string>
    <string name="reason_ela_inconsistent_risk">Normal editing, stickers, text overlays, and repeated exports can trigger this signal.</string>
    <string name="reason_metadata_implausible_label">METADATA</string>
    <string name="reason_metadata_implausible_title">Implausible metadata</string>
    <string name="reason_metadata_implausible_what">Embedded metadata does not match the media properties or expected capture path.</string>
    <string name="reason_metadata_implausible_why">Metadata mismatches can reveal tampering, synthetic export, or an inconsistent provenance chain.</string>
    <string name="reason_metadata_implausible_risk">Some authentic files have inconsistent metadata after editing, sharing, or platform processing.</string>
</resources>
